reviewloop.com 2015-12-30

# ReviewLoop Privacy Policy

ReviewLoop LLC (also referred to herein as “ReviewLoop”, “Company,” “this site,” “we,” “us,” “our,”), the operator of this website, respects the privacy of every individual who uses our site and its related services. We have made this Privacy Policy to make you understand what kind of information is collected by us, how we make use of it, and how we safeguard it in our website. This privacy policy applies to this website and all its related services. Usage of our site signifies your approval to this document. If you disagree with any part of this privacy policy, you may not use or access this site and its related services.

_**Information Collection**_

We generally collect three types of information from users. These are: Personally Identifiable Information which may include users first and last name, contact address, and phone number. Non-personally Identifiable Information  like users’ IP address, operating system, browser software, Internet Service Provider, domain type, and other numeric codes which identify a computer. And Personal Information such as email addresses when users subscribe to features such as opt-in newsletters, alerts, special promotions, etc.

Users should not send any confidential proprietary information via this site. If the visitor provides any such information, they are granting the site unrestricted, irrevocable, royalty free license to use, reproduce , display and distribute the information to its affiliates, partners etc. Users should not provide any information or material that is defamatory, obscene, harassing or unlawful or that incorporates the proprietary material of another site.

_**Usage of Information**_

Personally Identifiable Information is used mainly for identifying, managing and servicing individual users. Non-personally Identifiable Information is used to compile aggregate statistics on the number of users in the site, their demographics, interests, behavior etc. Personal Information is generally used to send emails about any promotions, newsletters, notices and alerts.

For the purpose of developing the business, the assets can be sold at any time. In such cases, user information, including Personally Identifiable Information  are also transferred as part of business assets. The users should agree that their data may be transferred to third parties in such circumstances.

_**Third-Party Integration**_

We may have partner relationships with third parties, and our site may contain any of the following: third-party API integration, advertisements, or links to external sites. In such cases, we may share Non-personally Identifiable Information or Personal Information with said third parties.  We do not share Personally Identifiable Information with such partners.

_**Cookies**_

The site uses cookies, to identify visitors for its internal use. A cookie is a tiny piece of data that is sent to the user’s browser which is stored in the computer. The cookies help the site to recognize the visitor when the visitor returns to the site.

 _ **Disclosure of Information to Competent Authorities**_

ReviewLoop has the right to disclose any information including personal information to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request.

_**Data Protection and Storage**_

We exert exhaustive efforts to safeguard the personal information provided by you. We employ several internal security mechanisms in our website which aim to protect your personal information. These include passwords, firewall, encryption, change control mechanisms, etc. However, it must also be remembered that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium.  ReviewLoop will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to unforeseeable errors, or to unauthorized acts of third parties.

_**Minimum Age**_

This site is intended for visitors above 18 years of age. Any user below that age should not provide any information to this site without the consent of a guardian.

_**Modifications to Privacy Policy**_

As a result of the constant changes with Internet technology, our Privacy Policy may also undergo frequent modifications. While trying to improve the services and products offered by this site, we may choose to extend the scope of the site in procuring data from its users. We reserve the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice, and the current Privacy Policy will be deemed effective. It is the responsibility of the users of this site to refer to this document regarding any future modifications to it.

If you have any questions or comments on this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.
